Smith, G.P. mss., 1965-2010 LMC 1981
Lilly Library
Smith, G.P. mss.
1965-2010
Lilly Library
Smith, George P., 1939-
LMC 1981
1 Box 1 standard
22 bound
The Smith, G.P. mss., 1965-, consists of the writings and papers of Catholic University of America law professor George P. Smith II, 1939-.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Many collections are housed offsite; retrieval requires advance notice. Please make an appointment a minimum of one week in advance of your visit.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift: 1987-2012
Biographical Note
George P. Smith, II, 1939-, is a law professor at the Catholic University of America in Washington, D.C.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of the writings and papers of George P. Smith. Also present is some memorabilia from the 10th and 25th reunions of Wabash High School's Class of 1957.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series: I. Personal and Professional files, II. Professional Volumes
Smith, George P., II (George Patrick), 1939-
- Personal & Professional Files
  - Selected Decisions: Foreign Claims Settlement Commission. United Departments of State. George P. Smith, II., 1966 (Box 1)
  - A Study of Selected Management Policies and Practices of the United States Air Force. Prepared by the President's Private Sector Survey Task Force. Final Report, July-October 1982 (Box 1)
  - Wabash High School: One Hundred Years (Box 1)
  - Wabash High School, Class of 1957 (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes items related to the class' 10th & 25th Reunions, as well as biographical sketches of the 25 year life cycle of the graduates and High School newspaper accounts. Wabash, Indiana
  - Report of Commissions: Presidential Letter of Recommendation of Commissions Lecter. Newspaper Reports in work of Commissions (Box 1)
  - President's Private Sector Survey on Cost Control: Report on the Department of the Air Force. Approved by the Subcommittee for the Full Executive Committee, Spring-Fall 1983 (Box 1)
  - The President's Private Sector Survey: Task Force Briefing. Department of the Air Force, June 1982 (Box 1)
  - The President's Private Sector Survey: Task Force on Department of the Air Force. Briefing materials, June 1982 (Box 1)
  - The Planning, Programming & Budgeting System (PPBS): A Primer, (3rd Edition). Directorate of Programs & Evaluation - AF/PRP; DCS/Programs & Resources, Department of the Air Force. Washington D.C., November 1981 (Box 1)
  - G.P. Smith: President's Private Sector Survey (Box 1)
  - One uncanceled, stamped envelope commemorating the second inauguration of Ronald Regan (Box 2)
- Professional Volumes
  Scope and Content Note
  This series includes 21 separate volumes of the works and papers of George P. Smith.
  - George P. Smith, II. Writings, 1965-1971 (Bound 1)
  - Writings of George P. Smith, II., February, 1965-February, 1971 (Bound 2)
  - George P. Smith, II. Writings, 1972-1977 (Bound 3)
  - G.P.S., II. Writings, 1971-1978 (Bound 4)
  - George P. Smith, II. Writings, 1980-1985 (Bound 5)
  - Health Law Journal. G.P. Smith, Dedicatory Issue, 1986 (Bound 6)
  - George P. Smith. Writings, 1970-1986 (Bound 7)
  - George P. Smith. Writings, 1978-1986 (Bound 8)
  - George P. Smith. Writings, 1981-1986 (Bound 9)
  - George P. Smith, II. Writings, 1982-86 (Bound 10)
  - George P. Smith, II. Papers, 1982-1988 (Bound 11)
  - George P. Smith, II. Selected Writings, 1962-1992 (Bound 12)
  - Published Writings of George P. Smith, II., 1986-1995 (Bound 13)
  - Monographs, George P. Smith, II., 1996-97 (Bound 14)
  - Published and Unpublished Papers. George P. Smith, II., 1993-2000 (Bound 15)
  - Published Articles: George P. Smith, II., 1994-2001 (Bound 16)
  - Monographs, George P. Smith, II., 1998-2001 (Bound 17)
  - A Citation Survey, G.P. Smith Writings, 2002 (Bound 18)
  - Law, Religion, and Medical Science. George P. Smith, II., 2003 (Bound 19)
  - Prof. George P. Smith, II. Catholic University Law School. Washington, D.C., 1977-2004 (Bound 20)
  - George P. Smith, II. Papers and Writings, 1999-2002 (Bound 21)